Unnumbered photographs
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Unnumbered photographs, 2.1.3.1.1.8
  - Unnumbered photographs: Afghanistan, 1921 - 1922; 5 (Box 1508)
    - Sir Francis Humphrys H.B.M. envoy Pleni- and Ambassador Extraor[dinary] - in Afghanistan, 4
    - Verso: Sir Francis Humphrys H.B.M. envoy Pleni- and Ambassador Extraor[dinary] - in Afghanistan, 4-verso
  - Unnumbered photographs: Afghanistan, 1921 - 1922; 6 (Box 1508)
    - Sir Francis Humphrys and staff, 1
    - Verso: Sir Francis Humphrys and staff, 1-verso
    - The university of Kabul and a vendor of smoke-like vegetables, 2
    - Verso: The university of Kabul and a vendor of smoke-like vegetables, 2-verso
    - In the garden of the Amir's summer palace, 3
    - Verso: In the garden of the Amir's summer palace, 3-verso
    - At the gate to the walled city of Jellalabad, 4
    - Verso: At the gate to the walled city of Jellalabad, 4-verso
  Box 1509
- Unnumbered photographs, 2.1.3.1.1.8
  - Unnumbered photographs: Afghanistan, 1921 - 1922; 1 (Box 1509)
    - [no description], 1
    - [no description], 2
    - [no description], 3
    - [no description], 4
    - [no description], 5
  - Unnumbered photographs: Afghanistan, 1921 - 1922; 2 (Box 1509)
    - [no description], 1
    - [no description], 2
    - [no description], 3
    - [no description], 4
  - Unnumbered photographs: Afghanistan - Amir Amanullah Khan, 3 (Box 1509)
    - His Majesty Amanulla Khan the Amir of Afghanistan (on left) with one of his brothers. This is the first time a photograph of the ruler of Afghans hs been ?] - It is taken from the Lowell Thomas Travelogu "Romantic India" in which scenes from the forbidden country play an important part, 1
    - Verso: His Majesty Amanulla Khan the Amir of Afghanistan (on left) with one of his brothers. This is the first time a photograph of the ruler of Afghans hs been ?] - It is taken from the Lowell Thomas Travelogu "Romantic India" in which scenes from the forbidden country play an important part, 1-verso
    - [no description] (7 copies), 2